The morning chimes have rung, and it's us.
This is Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku!
Today, we, the members who don't play games at all, decided to play a horror game.
We're going to play a horror game, I guess you'd call it.
This time, we'd like to play a game called "Exit 8" which has been talked about a lot.
Exit 8" is a game that has been talked about a lot.
If you don't find something strange and do something, it will never end.
That's what the staff said earlier.
There are three of us, so we'll keep a close eye on things.
We'll do it, if there are three of us.
I've heard that those who can do it well finish early.
I've heard that before.
They finish quickly and easily.
Let's get it over with.
Let's go for it.
Okay, we'll take turns with the controllers.
I'm going to turn it around.
Okay, let's get started.
Here we go.
GO!
I'll go first.
I'm just going to walk this one off, right?
Just keep walking.
Find anything out of the ordinary?
Just keep a close eye on it.
Wait, I'm terrible at this.
I've never done this before. I've only played Mario Kart.
Odd, odd, odd.
Oh, I see. I see.
If I do it like this, I can drive.
Oh! I see.
I have to run, I have to run... a little bit slower.
Slow down.
Slow down, slow down, slow down.
You're driving on the left side of the road, right?
Zero.
What do you mean, zero?
It means there's something wrong.
This is the first time. It's nothing.
There's an anomaly between just now and right where we're going.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh! Pops is here.
I guess this means we have to go back.
No?
Is it okay with you?
He said it's okay.
I'm sure there's a sign or something.
Uncle Dan, Uncle Dan... you have a pediatrician's haircut.
It's so cool.
Uncle Dandy's uncle.
I really have no idea.
Did you see anything weird?
I didn't find it.
I couldn't find it either.
That's a tough one.
But zero means it was there.
The numbers haven't changed.
If you found something unusual, it would be 1 now.
Now it's 0, so we have to go up to 8.
Isn't it hard to get to 8?
Oh, no.
Memory.
I'm looking for a part time job.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's hard.
Late camera is working
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I don't get it.
Zero. Why is that? Why don't you slow down and take a look? Sure, let's stop and take a look.
Let's take a slow look at the sign.
It says "member for 8 days.
It's the same.
Is this one okay?
That's a part-time job.
What, you don't think this is the place?
Maybe it's this kind of place.
Are you okay?
Eyes.
Sparkle above the eyes.
This one's okay, too.
I'll wait for Satouki one more time.
This way?
I didn't see you looking this way.
Let's try again later.
I'll take another look.
Oh, I have no idea.
Let's back up.
I haven't done that at all.
It's a little bit like that one, isn't it?
If we don't move fast, we'll be like that for the rest of our lives.
Maybe we should run.
All the way to the left.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Where are you looking?
Where, where, where?
Heh heh heh heh heh.
Is it this way? Up?
Because this one's facing away from us.
Forward. Forward?
Maybe if we move it this way, it'll face forward.
This way, this way?
This way, this way, this way.
Oh.
Thank you very much. I keep running into that card.
Oh, here it is. Here's the sign.
The notice.
Tight.
August 8th. Are you okay?
We're looking for part-timers.
What are you looking for?
Justice.
What? This one hasn't changed.
I don't think it's changed.
What?
The work line...
I have no idea.
Oh, this one's changed?
What?
I don't understand.
No, it's not going anywhere.
Are you saying that it's possible that there was nothing unusual just now?
Yes, that's true.
If I'm in first place next time.
I'll never be able to do this operation.
It is difficult. There is no anomaly.
On the left side of the road.
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
This way.
That's no good. What? Why not?
You didn't change when you got up, did you? Let's take our time.
Disagreement. That's great.
White Asmiru candy?
2023, August 8. 9:13.
It's okay.
Nerves of a healthy belly for all of you.
Oh, my gosh. It's all there. Where people are standing.
Part-time, part-50.
Cashier serving customers.
BLC Store.
NEW OPEN. 19 December.
Dogs. Jumping course.
Shampoo.
Jump course.
Local first time.
Make-up art.
December 15. 17.
Moviefest. Fashionable tickets. Yes.
I'll take a look at the other way around?
I'm sorry, I don't know how to operate this.
So you're going to turn it this way? Oh, I've got it.
For business use,
The distribution board room.
Yes, sir. How about this side?
Uh, billing.
Yes, okay. Did you see it? Yes, I did.
The sign.
Maybe we should just run.
Slow down a little bit.
It's definitely in the middle. Like someone who doesn't manage organic alcohol in Mario Kart.
Two on the left.
They haven't changed.
Why? They didn't change earlier.
Well, sometimes it's there, sometimes it's not, and sometimes it wasn't.
I see. Next time, there'll be something different.
It runs when you push it. Push it?
That's right.
Be careful around here.
What about you? Is he okay? Is he the same? Uncle hasn't changed.
With a smile 8 Part-time job, messy
Ta-da!
What?
First of all, I need time for this...
Oh, no!
You scared me.
I'm so sorry.
I was trying to be really funny.
It's okay.
Wen-den guard room.
It hasn't changed.
local scrivener
okay, okay, for business
Business clerk.
What's this one?
Cleaner.
No change.
This place hasn't changed, that's for sure.
One.
This way?
Too fast.
You suck at this.
It's too hard.
I think I'll just put this here.
This part didn't change.
I'm not sure I'll make it to eight.
It happens.
It's gonna be okay.
New pump from 9:00 to 13:00?
Yes, sir.
Yeah, I'll be fine.
This won't change.
It'll be fine.
Your grandfather hasn't changed either.
Wasn't he wearing socks?
Was he wearing socks?
It's such a small detail.
No, it's not.
Why doesn't he dodge?
You look great, Grandpa.
You sure? You don't have to chase after him.
I spilled shampoo.
Yes, it's okay.
I understand.
Okay.
What's the difference?
It's okay. It's okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
I think I got it a little backwards.
Let it hang down once.
Can you turn it up a little bit?
What? It's back.
What's wrong?
Is this your uncle's sock?
Uncle's socks?
Try on the salmon pink ones.
Did I put them on?
That's what No-No-Kichan said earlier.
When you said he was wearing socks.
Didn't you have them on earlier?
What?
You're wearing them.
I'm wearing them.
They're the same. You haven't changed.
What's the difference?
Screwing customers.
Not here?
It's never not here.
What changes except here?
It changes.
Is it a sign or something up there?
What's up there? On this side,
I found the underground plaza.
What? There wasn't a sign here, was there?
There it is.
It's an underground plaza.
Let's check here, too. Next. Sure. Maybe we were close to that place earlier.
Maybe it's not there. There might be.
Video camera is working. Yes, it is.
It's difficult. Difficult. Difficult to operate.
Oh, you didn't do it earlier.
Let's look at Uncle Dan's square next time. Sure.
Didn't you see it here? A poster. No.
Not here? It's not here. It's not here.
It was one more block in front of it.
Is it up there?
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, we're going back!
It's the other way! Back!
Go back! Go back!
Is that it? Turn around.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Where are we going back to?
This way?
Oh, here it comes! I see it!
There's so many bees.
Chance, I feel better.
Okay, here we go.
Go ahead and down.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Where's your uncle?
Yes, he's here.
Hasn't he changed?
What about that one over here?
He's back where he was.
Where is it? Where was it?
Look again.
It's right there.
This is the point.
Yes.
Is it right?
It's right.
This is right, too.
Yes, it's right.
It's the same here.
I see. So it's the other way around.
Indeed.
On the left.
Oh, 3!
That's good.
Oh, it's the other way.
It's running.
The other way.
That was scary. I was.
Here they come. I see. That's what I mean.
I'm starting to get it.
So, can I do a little more?
Can I do a little more?
Not at all.
This is fun. It is.
Will it be different after the next round?
We're the same.
The guy who just came in was the one who told me about you.
I was remembering he was dead.
I thought it was too soon.
I think we're okay here.
Let's do it suddenly.
Over there.
There's the back door.
Okay, next. Yuna, please.
Is it 5 now?
Dance.
If I miss this one time, it'll be 1.
Oh, it's difficult.
That's what I mean.
Let's do our best. Hurry up, hurry up.
You like this?
Okay, and the sign, too.
It's okay. Drieve 8 in Kim Yong will be fine.
There's also an underground plaza behind this one.
There it is.
Maybe we should look at that too.
I'm not scared.
It's okay, it's okay.
Oh, if it's scary, it's water, isn't it?
Full Piatti pads.
It's okay. It's open.
It's okay. Security collars are on their way.
What's this way?
Underground plaza.
It hasn't changed. - It hasn't changed.
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
Scary, scary, scary, scary.
Afraid, afraid, afraid, afraid
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Go, go, go, go, go, go
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
A-ha-ha-ha-ha
Oh no, it's huge!
Grandpa, you don't get that much.
You're a really bad grandpa. Not good.
He said don't stop, we stopped too. I can't say.
How's it look? Zero.
You want to do it? Go on.
That was a little scary.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Did you turn your grandfather's off?
You mean that was a bad one? Oh, that's what you mean.
Hey, hey, look! Uncle, behind you, there's some kind of human shape.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no!
Up, up, up! Up! Up! Up!
This way? Back this way? Yes, back this way.
Okay, one. Oh, one!
But I'm starting to feel like a follower.
I'm starting to get it. I see.
So maybe it's not a sign detail or something.
Indeed.
Maybe it's not that kind of detail.
The big letters on the top, they've changed.
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Uncle?
You!
Uncle!
Just now...
Your eyebrows are so beautiful.
You look beautiful today.
Are you okay?
I'm fine as long as I stay close.
What?
You scared me. You scared me.
But I'm a little scared.
You look the same.
It's okay. It's okay.
Wasn't this real?
I think it was the left side.
It's okay.
Well, go ahead, Konno-san.
All right. Let's go for it. Did we go to 4 earlier?
We're up to 4, right?
Let's go for it.
Uncle is here.
Maybe he's coming out late, too.
Maybe.
Maybe he's a little late.
Don't worry, don't worry. I've got the best hands.
Hon no te nakachan.
Here you go.
Hey...
That hurts.
Huh?
Oh!
Please go back. Please go back.
Run, run.
Yes, yes, yes.
Uncle a minute.
Go back, go back, go back.
Don't come any closer.
You didn't want him to catch up with you, did you?
I didn't.
It's okay. Maybe that's not what I meant.
Oh, that's what I mean.
It's just a little flicker or something.
It's making a strange sound.
It's flickering.
It's okay, it's okay. Pops is fine.
It's okay, it's okay.
The valve chamber.
There's no valve chamber.
There's no valve chamber. Let's go back.
We'll be greeted by an uncle.
It's good, isn't it? It's going well, isn't it?
Here we are.
I want to go next.
Go, go, go. Go, go, go. Let's go.
I want to go this far.
Someone's in danger.
Is there something wrong with this one while it's running?
I'm sure of it.
There he is.
What about the near plaza?
I'm sure.
It's all right. There's not much of a plaza in the vicinity.
What about the movie?
What?
Oh, here it is.
Here it comes. Good luck.
Thank you very much.
motherboard
It's all right, isn't it?
What's that? It's not here. It's here.
It's working.
Two more.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You scared me.
Excuse me.
Let's do the next one.
Rust.
I'll be sad if they go back.
The two of us together, after all we've been through.
I'm scared.
Uncle Dan, do you feel safe?
I feel safe, Uncle.
Thank you for everything.
You haven't changed. You haven't changed.
But, you know, there's no reason why there shouldn't be a change at the end of the day.
Indeed.
Because, you know, there was a change that was pretty obvious.
Oh, my God! Are you all right? You scared me.
I thought you were turning your head to the side. Your eyes.
I'm fine. You scared me. I only saw it from the side.
I'm starting to see all kinds of weird things.
It's not there.
No, it doesn't.
No?
That's it, isn't it? It's a little bit.
Whoaaaaaaaaaaaa.
Yes. Let's go for it.
Let's go.
Hey, why?
The eyes on the poster?
What? The eyes on the poster?
What? I knew it. Oh, yeah.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Hmm?
Because there aren't any here, until a couple of pairs.
No, it's not here.
So that means that exit 8 is the other way around or something.
Wow, it looks like they're making their own.
Is that weird? Is that strange?
I never saw that before.
Should we change it?
Never mind.
Was that weird?
Oh, it was weird.
You look at it so much.
I thought you were looking at me a lot. Right now.
I don't know, I'm seeing so many people's eyes moving around. I'm sure.
Their eyes were moving.
That was weird. I couldn't tell.
It's okay, it's okay. It's okay.
You haven't changed.
TMR.
That's it. Thank you for watching.
Left side?
Can we get something on the right side here?
A glance.
It didn't change.
Sometimes my heart is pounding.
The sudden darkening was bad, wasn't it?
This place, though, is not on the inside.
The sign hasn't changed.
The sign doesn't change unexpectedly, does it?
Seriously!
Aaaaah!!!
It's stupid, stupid, stupid.
Hahaha, early, terrible.
Snowball, your uncle, why isn't it playing?
Shall we do it now?
And everyone says I control ahhh...
No one else does!
I'm borrowing it. I'm borrowing it. I have to be careful.
Oh, no, no, no, I threw it, I threw it.
You didn't have water earlier.
No, no, no, no.
It's a little bit different.
It's not exactly the same.
Maybe it's still the same, maybe it's still the same.
It's like...
Oh, really?
It's okay.
I'm fine.
You haven't changed. You haven't changed. Finally.
Oh, man, this is taking forever.
We're up to seven. I'd like to go.
Oh, my God.
My heart is racing.
That was scary.
So you haven't changed?
No, I haven't changed at all.
I'm getting used to it.
Oh, it's thick, thick, thick.
Uh, hot.
Oh, that was scary.
Scary! Why is it that color?
What is that red stuff, fish?
Fish?
The red stuff that came down the river.
I thought it was just red water.
It's okay. It's okay.
What?
It's not your brother?
Is he your brother, too?
He's not my brother?
He hasn't changed.
I'm fine.
Okay, good.
Underground plaza's clear.
All right, all right, all right.
Is there traffic on the left?
Oh, it's still the same.
Oh, there it is. There it is.
There it is.
I think it was just here or something.
No, Oster. No, Oster, no.
What?
No, Oster, no.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, I'm coming back. I'm coming back.
Yes, I'm coming back.
Bugs!
I'm scared.
Mr. Bug!
Why are you so scary?
Why did you make it such a scary field?
Mr. Bug!
It's nothing to do with you, Uncle.
It's okay. I'm back.
That was scary, what happened back there.
It's okay.
I don't want to talk to you. I'm scared.
You haven't changed.
I was scared.
That's great, Yuna.
Thank you.
That was good. It's good, it's good. You're getting faster.
It's good.
You haven't changed at all. You've changed a lot. Earlier.
I was scared. That guy was the scariest.
It's okay.
I'm fine.
Thank you for seeing me this far.
Everyone, look down at the red and yellow lights, because they may have changed.
The light above may have changed, so look up.
Look at the poster. Are those handcuffs on the door?
The robes are in different positions.
Oh, wow.
Uncle may have changed a little bit, so look closely.
Uncle Dan, this way.
Yes, Uncle.
And down there? Down there too?
Ceiling.
And up?
You mean up there, like this, like that?
I mean, I don't like it when there's something up there.
Which part? The one that you turn.
The bottom part.
Turn it, right.
And you're okay around here, right?
Okay, here we go.
Did I just miss my eye?
What?
Did your eye move?
I don't know. I didn't think they moved.
I thought I saw something move just now.
I'm not so sure now.
It's moving? Here.
Let's go!
It's like the whole place has changed.
It's like a plaza.
Oh, sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, it's good, it's good, it's good.
Yes, it is.
Here we are.
Important.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
I'm with you.
You have an uncle?
You have an uncle.
I don't know, maybe our hands are different heights or something.
Is that possible?
You're okay now, right?
I'm fine.
It's a little harder.
You're gonna be okay.
Oh, what?
What?
What's changed?
It just happened.
I can't tell if you've changed.
He's thinner.
I don't think so.
It's the ceiling down there, too.
You haven't changed at all.
How is it? It's the same.
It's the same.
Oh, my God! It's open!
Let's get out of here! Yes!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
People are going to come out, aren't they? It's just like that.
If we stay there like that.
People are going to come out and move.
Did you open a window?
The one at the far end.
Did it open?
It just slammed. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
Fuji hasn't changed.
The River of Formosan? Is the River of Formosan alright?
How about your eyes? Eyes are difficult.
Ehhhh... Hedgehog, please.
It's difficult.
What? I fell. Back, back, back.
That's great. Everything is different.
I see.
When I walk, I'm slow, but when I run, I'm fast.
We're right in the middle.
It's the same.
No change.
No, it hasn't.
The weather is glowing. No change in Pops either.
Thanks for your help.
Are you all right?
What part of the body is so weight negative?
This way? This way?
Over here.
I think I'm breathing.
I wish you'd stop making this noise.
Number two.
Yeah, it's fine.
You haven't changed.
What do you have, Uri? I thought you had one.
I thought you had a smartphone.
No change?
No change.
Okay, let's go.
Okay. Please do.
What? Please.
Mister?
Yes, I'm here.
But I'm going to win.
Good morning, sir.
What? You're not okay?
You were looking down there, too.
It's a display block, right?
Okay.
Let's go.
Why?
I don't know.
What is it?
Did you find it? Just now.
What? Wait a minute.
I know you have an uncle.
I know you're in there, Uncle.
Okay, Uncle.
It's okay.
You're gonna learn.
You're okay. You're okay.
You're smiling!
Uncle Dan, you're smiling!
You scared me!
He's laughing!
What?
You're laughing! I said it.
I've never seen an uncle laughing before.
He's laughing.
He was laughing.
You scared me. I'm afraid of being lost.
Uncle Dan, you're both relieved and scared. That's true.
It's okay, Uncle.
That's right, twice in a row.
Uncle Dan, you were laughing so much.
I was so surprised.
He was laughing so hard just now.
He was laughing so hard.
I was scared.
What the hell?
I don't know.
Where is it?
Let's repeat this once before we come here.
Yes.
Before we do it again, why don't we look behind us?
You mean here? Here?
On the last turn,
Oh, I see what you mean. You haven't changed.
You haven't changed, have you? You haven't grown taller.
I wonder if he ever grows taller.
It's open!
Yes, yes, yes.
Was it open?
It's open.
Oh, it was kind of dark.
Oh, my God!
Where was it open?
I'm getting ahead of myself.
We've got to find it.
Uncle Dan, did you do something?
You're doing something. Look.
There's something white on your face.
What did you do?
Uncle Dan, what did you do? Are you okay?
I just got cream on my face.
It feels good. He grabbed me.
Oh, shit. There it is.
As usual, I only notice the changes in my uncle.
I'm sure.
It's okay.
It's all right.
Miri, are you looking at me too?
The door's not open either.
Now we turn around.
Here?
It's scary to look back, isn't it?
It's okay.
Oh, it's up.
It's a little scary here, too.
I can imagine the strange way the man I once saw ran.
I want to see it too.
He's kind of walking on high.
Something like a giant.
That was fun.
You're okay, right?
I've been avoiding you.
I'm scared.
I'm afraid to look back.
Hi.
There's nothing here.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Okay, well, let's just go this far.
Please.
I want to do this while I'm drinking water.
It's opening. We have to be careful.
It hasn't changed. It hasn't changed.
It hasn't changed.
You haven't changed.
You haven't changed. I'm afraid to turn around.
Okay.
Okay. I'll turn around.
Oh, it's okay.
You haven't changed.
Why is that?
I'm scared.
Why are you scared? You didn't change.
Here you go.
Oh, no. I want to go to number 8, but we only went to 7.
Here?
You see this?
It looks distorted.
Maybe I'm wrong.
It's the same. It's still the same.
You're just messing with it.
Don't mess it up.
Leave my hair open. I'm sweating.
Now, the usual assault of terror.
Your eyes are narrow.
I'm fine. You just lost your uncle.
It's right here.
Shut up!
I see.
That's why we have to look everywhere.
I've been following you.
Oh, another doll.
Did you get lost?
He stops every time.
Where am I?
I was so scared.
I was following you.
It's scary that you're following me.
It's okay.
Are those stairs?
There are stairs.
I'm with my uncle.
Oh, here they come.
Are you okay? Yeah, I'm fine.
Did you see that light over there?
It was glowing.
Are you okay?
Uji, is everything okay?
I'm fine.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Aahhh!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
This way, this way, this way.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
It's okay.
Oh, he got away.
If he gets away, he'll grow up, won't he?
It's a growth spurt if you can get away with it.
I couldn't escape earlier. I got caught up in it.
I'm scared.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
I'm excited about something important.
I'm fine.
I'm the same.
I'm tired.
You haven't changed.
Are you okay?
I'll look back.
You look normal.
Okay, that's enough.
Please.
What was that?
It's not Cholo.
Oh, thank God.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I don't know if there's a sound or a beep.
Or lights going out?
Nothing's changed.
I'm not smiling.
Look back over here.
There's nothing.
Nothing's changed.
Are you all right?
You haven't changed.
Please.
Just what?
Why?
I went all the way up to 7.
I don't know.
I don't get it.
It hasn't changed.
I want to go to number 8.
I keep seeing this poster.
What?
Scary! It's horrible!
What's that noise? What's that?
It's the sound of a train.
I just heard a crack.
So mean.
I said, "Supervisor, snap!
I'm scared.
Hey...
Aaah!
That's great.
Isn't it kind of big?
Is he big?
It's growing.
You're kind of big, aren't you?
Wow. I knew there was something to grow.
He's growing.
He's a big guy.
He was big, wasn't he? He was pretty big.
He was pretty big.
He wasn't smiling.
The door was not open.
I'll look back.
Good night.
You're okay.
Ooh.
Three to go.
Four.
You haven't changed.
Now that's a surprise.
I don't think I could play a horror game.
Indeed.
I'll be fine.
Let's turn around.
You're going to look back from up there?
I'll be fine.
I don't hear a clunk.
I want to hear a clunk.
Oh! Three more to go! Let's go for it!
If I can do this!
Grandpa hasn't been running lately.
He's certainly been running.
I want to see every weird scene.
Are you okay?
Are you okay today?
No, I'm not.
Are you okay?
What was that? Is it on the door?
It's on the door.
Aah! It's in the middle!
I think it's better to do this with a big group.
It's amazing that people usually do it alone.
It's amazing that you can do it by yourself.
Wow! It's good.
Are you going to do it again? You, young lady.
Let's go for it!
Two more. You can do it.
Go!
I can do it.
I'm too good at this.
Exit.
It's still the same.
It hasn't changed.
You haven't changed.
Let's turn around
I'll turn around.
You're looking in my eyes, aren't you?
Come here.
Let's go this way.
It's moving.
Let's go back.
What? Amazing.
I think we're close to the finish line.
Here's another one.
I think I'm falling. He's definitely here.
Uncle.
Oh, we're up to seven. That's the last time I did that.
If I keep this up, I can make it to the finish line.
Oh, I saw a light. I was so surprised.
I thought it was a flicker.
It hasn't changed, it hasn't changed, it hasn't changed, it hasn't changed, it hasn't changed, it hasn't changed, it hasn't changed.
The door was still there.
The security cameras are working.
So let's turn around.
Hmm.
It's still the same, right?
It hasn't changed, has it?
It looks the same.
I'm scared.
You know, when you're Jarrod.
Please.
What's that? Is there gonna be another one? This one.
There's one more time.
I'm scared of one more.
There's gonna be another one? This one.
I'm scared one more time.
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm fine.
How's it going over here?
You haven't changed either.
He hasn't changed.
You see that light?
Let's just go around in a circle, shall we?
It's okay. It's okay.
You're not okay?
Oh, no. I'm scared.
Please. It says there's a way out.
Please. Exit, exit, exit.
Oh, wow!
Yay!
Wow! We're on the ground!
We're finally out!
Wow!
So, we cleared the memoto!
Yay!
I'm a beginner!
The stays were a little wobbly and wobbly until the very end.
It was solid, so I'll take it from here.
You did it!
I'm so happy!
But it was so hard!
But really, it was scary... halfway through.
I was scared!
Surprisingly, when I put the hot water on normally
The water came pouring out suddenly, and it just kept on pouring.
I didn't even want to see the weird way the old man was walking.
It was fun.
You know, Uncle?
He was laughing.
Do you have a repertoire for this?
It was difficult.
31!
I think there are 31.
How many did we get?
He said 23.
We ended up with eight.
So that's it.
I wonder what kind of weirdness is going on.
For me, the uncle's smile was a little...
That was scary.
It was a little scary.
It was scary that he was smiling.
He's not smiling!
What was it? His face was white.
I don't know what it was.
It was like a mask with something on it.
I don't know.
But I always noticed something strange about him.
Everyone was getting taller.
You've grown taller, Uncle. That's good.
Thank you, Uncle.
Thank you for all your hard work.
Beginner's horror game?
Is it a horror game or is it a live game?
Please subscribe to our channel, comment and give us a high rating!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
Nest Reborn Now